# FARAL LANINDI

+6285692358166 | farallanindi13@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/faral-lanindi-00b5421a7/ | https://linktr.ee/farallan

Jakarta Selatan

I have an experience in customer service with more than 1 year of experience. Have expertise in handling customer complaints, building and maintaining good relationships with customers, and being able to increase customer satisfaction. I have good communication skills, and can adapt to new environments. I have an interest in improving my abilities in the field of customer service and satisfaction.

## **Work Experiences**

## PT. Byebeli Inovasi Indonesia - Jakarta

Jan 2023 - Present

Customer Excellence Officer

- · Reply to incoming chats quickly, actively and effectively
- Providing good and responsive service to both B2C and B2B customers
- · Provide education to customers regarding the services offered
- · Understand customer needs in depth
- · Provide solutions to customer problems and complaints quickly and effectively
- Build and maintain long-term relationships with customers

fins\_mart - Jakarta Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

Admin Marketplace

- · Upload products to Marketplace
- · Receive, and process orders entered through the Marketplace
- · Reply to incoming chats quickly and accurately
- Provide solutions to complaints and complaints from customers
- · Conduct follow-up with potential customers
- · Checking regularly to stock and conditions product

## PT. Coway International Indonesia - Jakarta

May 2021 - Jun 2022

Admin Sales

- · Promote the product both directly and using a social media
- · Create content on social media and use the Ads feature as a promotional tool
- · Entry potential customer data into the database
- · Serving and responding to questions from customers both via chat and telephone
- · Conduct follow-up on potential customers

## Education

#### Vocational High School 59, in Major of Online Business and Marketing - Jakarta

Jun 2018 - Jun 2023

Vocational High School in, 8.50/10.00

## **Skills**

- Bahasa: Indonesia (Native), Inggris (Intermediate), TOEIC Score 688
- Softskills: Team Work, Time Management, Disciplined, Detail Oriented
- Hardskills: Microsoft Office, Basic Photo and Editing Video, Canva, Facebook dan Instagram Ads, Marketplace Mechanism